<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-11-25T15:15:23+01:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Made Up</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><author><name>Made Up</name></author><entry><title type="html">Villa Kerylos</title><link href="/Villa-Kerylos/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Villa Kerylos" /><published>2017-08-25T12:32:20+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-25T12:32:20+02:00</updated><id>/Villa-Kerylos</id><content type="html" xml:base="/Villa-Kerylos/">&lt;p&gt;Situated right on the Mediterranean Sea in Beaulieu-sur-Mer, sits the idyllic Villa Kerylos. Built in the early 20th Century, the greek inspired property is an architects dream and the perfect hide away for those wanting to escape the bright lights of Nice and Monaco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/VillaKerylos4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Yosh Ginsu&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From intricately hand-painted ceilings, to beautifully designed mosaic flooring, each room possesses it’s own unique characteristics dedicated to various greek gods and classical heroes. Adorned with various types of marble, The Andron or ‘Mens Lounge’ is particularly impressive, mirroring similar aspects of idesign and ambiance to that of the ‘Palais de Versailles.’ The interiors of this building truly define the meaning of luxury although it never feels ’too much’ in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/VillaKerylos9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Yosh Ginsu&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The flourishing gardens provide an equally beautiful and tranquil setting with views of the Mediterranean coastline stretching from Saint Jean Cap Ferrat to Cap d’Ail. Its one of those places where you could just sit, take a book and read all day without a care in the world. There are also numerous art exhibitions held throughout the year located in the Gallery of Antiques below the villa itself, perfectly curated to intertwine both modern and ancient works of art. Whatever the time of year, this is somewhere you’ll undoubtedly feel calm and inspired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/VillaKerylos10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Yosh Ginsu&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more details, visit the website at http://www.villakerylos.fr/en/&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Adam Neilson</name></author><category term="Blog" /><category term="Mountains" /><summary type="html">Situated right on the Mediterranean Sea in Beaulieu-sur-Mer, sits the idyllic Villa Kerylos. Built in the early 20th Century, the greek inspired property is an architects dream and the perfect hide away for those wanting to escape the bright lights of Nice and Monaco.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Saint Paul de Vence</title><link href="/Saint-Paul-de-Vence/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Saint Paul de Vence" /><published>2017-08-24T12:32:20+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-24T12:32:20+02:00</updated><id>/Saint-Paul-de-Vence</id><content type="html" xml:base="/Saint-Paul-de-Vence/">&lt;p&gt;Located on a hillside just 20km away from Nice, sits one of my favourite places of all time, Saint Paul de Vence. What can only be described as a historical labyrinth, the streets of Saint Paul de Vence are lined with art galleries, restaurants, churches and of course your typical provencal boutiques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/SaintPaul5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Yosh Ginsu&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting with the galleries, the amount and variety is outstanding, particularly when you consider the size of the small medieval town. There are two in particular that stand out and of course, when it comes to art, everyone has their own preference. But for me, the ODD Gallery and Galerie du Vieux Saint Paul are my personal favourites. The Galerie du Vieux Saint Paul often houses a wide selection of Dali and Lothar sculptures for example whilst the ODD Gallery displays a variety of powerful photography and sculptural pieces produced by up and coming artists including Pierre Taurtaut who’s photography work is just beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/SaintPaul6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Yosh Ginsu&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the town itself is just as inspiring; the architecture, the atmosphere, the views. From the distinctive cobbled streets, to the abundance of floral archways and bronze statues, Saint Paul de Vence is truly worth visiting. Even before entering the Village itself, it’s worth taking a little detour through the hills where you’ll not only find the perfect view of Saint Paul, but also a number of abandoned and derelict chapels bringing a further element of mystery to the place.
In regards to restaurants and cafes, I cannot recommend enough Restaurant Le Tilleul although I’ll admit, there’s often a waiting list depending on the time of year. I’ve always been impressed by the service and quality of food which explains why this restaurant in particular is so popular amongst both tourists and locals.
With that said, we’re honestly spoilt for choice when it comes to where and what we can eat.
Saint Paul de Vence is perhaps one of the most impressive villages along the Cote d’Azur and somewhere worth revisiting over and over again thanks to the rotating art exhibitions keeping this little medieval town alive. I’ve never visited anywhere quite like it which is why, in my opinion, it really is somewhere quite special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/SaintPaul.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Yosh Ginsu&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Made Up</name></author><category term="Blog" /><category term="Sunset" /><summary type="html">Located on a hillside just 20km away from Nice, sits one of my favourite places of all time, Saint Paul de Vence. What can only be described as a historical labyrinth, the streets of Saint Paul de Vence are lined with art galleries, restaurants, churches and of course your typical provencal boutiques.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Life in Nice</title><link href="/Nice/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Life in Nice" /><published>2017-08-23T12:32:20+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-23T12:32:20+02:00</updated><id>/Nice</id><content type="html" xml:base="/Nice/">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Made Up</name></author><category term="Blog" /><category term="Meditation" /><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Season in Ibiza</title><link href="/Ibiza/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Season in Ibiza" /><published>2017-08-21T12:32:20+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-21T12:32:20+02:00</updated><id>/Ibiza</id><content type="html" xml:base="/Ibiza/">&lt;p&gt;This is going back five years, but is an experience I’ll never forget. It doesn’t matter the kind of person you are, I think it’s important to step out of your comfort zone and try something new. After living and working in London for almost four years, I decided to break the exhausting routine that was my life at the time. Moving out to Ibiza for the Summer was one of the best decisions I’ve ever made and taught me a lot about what I want out of life. I worked for both a private yacht trip company and a scuba diving school which meant that every single day, I was working on the harbour, five metres from the sea. I worked seven days a week and sometimes it was really hard, but simply being on ‘The White Isle’ as it’s known, made it all worth it; the sun, the music, the atmosphere and most of all, my friends. Being able to go to the beach or boat parties any time of the week, every day is different and the opportunities are always there to meet interesting people. With all that said, you need to have a thick skin to survive the season especially considering that sleep is a real luxury out there. Obviously this massively depends on where you are on the island, however if you’re based in Sant Antonio, be prepared for the chaos that is the West End.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Made Up</name></author><category term="Blog" /><category term="Mountains" /><category term="Sport" /><summary type="html">This is going back five years, but is an experience I’ll never forget. It doesn’t matter the kind of person you are, I think it’s important to step out of your comfort zone and try something new. After living and working in London for almost four years, I decided to break the exhausting routine that was my life at the time. Moving out to Ibiza for the Summer was one of the best decisions I’ve ever made and taught me a lot about what I want out of life. I worked for both a private yacht trip company and a scuba diving school which meant that every single day, I was working on the harbour, five metres from the sea. I worked seven days a week and sometimes it was really hard, but simply being on ‘The White Isle’ as it’s known, made it all worth it; the sun, the music, the atmosphere and most of all, my friends. Being able to go to the beach or boat parties any time of the week, every day is different and the opportunities are always there to meet interesting people. With all that said, you need to have a thick skin to survive the season especially considering that sleep is a real luxury out there. Obviously this massively depends on where you are on the island, however if you’re based in Sant Antonio, be prepared for the chaos that is the West End.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Monaco</title><link href="/Monaco/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Monaco" /><published>2017-08-20T12:32:20+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-20T12:32:20+02:00</updated><id>/Monaco</id><content type="html" xml:base="/Monaco/">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Made Up</name></author><category term="Blog" /><category term="Meditation" /><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Antelope Canyon</title><link href="/Antelope-Canyon/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Antelope Canyon" /><published>2017-08-18T12:32:20+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-18T12:32:20+02:00</updated><id>/Antelope-Canyon</id><content type="html" xml:base="/Antelope-Canyon/">&lt;p&gt;Located on a hillside just 20km away from Nice, sits one of my favourite places of all time, Saint Paul de Vence. What can only be described as a historical labyrinth, the streets of Saint Paul de Vence are lined with art galleries, restaurants, churches and of course your typical provencal boutiques. Starting with the galleries, the amount and variety is outstanding, particularly when you consider the size of the small medieval town. There are two in particular that stand out and of course, when it comes to art, everyone has their own preference. But for me, the ODD Gallery and Galerie du Vieux Saint Paul are my personal favourites. The Galerie du Vieux Saint Paul often houses a wide selection of Dali and Lothar sculptures for example whilst the ODD Gallery displays a variety of powerful photography and sculptural pieces produced by up and coming artists including Pierre Taurtaut who’s photography work is just beautiful.
But the town itself is just as inspiring; the architecture, the atmosphere, the views. From the distinctive cobbled streets, to the abundance of floral archways and bronze statues, Saint Paul de Vence is truly worth visiting. Even before entering the Village itself, it’s worth taking a little detour through the hills where you’ll not only find the perfect view of Saint Paul, but also a number of abandoned and derelict chapels bringing a further element of mystery to the place.
In regards to restaurants and cafes, I cannot recommend enough Restaurant Le Tilleul although I’ll admit, there’s often a waiting list depending on the time of year. I’ve always been impressed by the service and quality of food which explains why this restaurant in particular is so popular amongst both tourists and locals. But again, we’re honestly spoilt for choice when it comes to where and what we can eat.
Saint Paul de Vence is perhaps one of the most impressive villages along the Cote d’Azur.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Made Up</name></author><category term="Blog" /><category term="Sunset" /><summary type="html">Located on a hillside just 20km away from Nice, sits one of my favourite places of all time, Saint Paul de Vence. What can only be described as a historical labyrinth, the streets of Saint Paul de Vence are lined with art galleries, restaurants, churches and of course your typical provencal boutiques. Starting with the galleries, the amount and variety is outstanding, particularly when you consider the size of the small medieval town. There are two in particular that stand out and of course, when it comes to art, everyone has their own preference. But for me, the ODD Gallery and Galerie du Vieux Saint Paul are my personal favourites. The Galerie du Vieux Saint Paul often houses a wide selection of Dali and Lothar sculptures for example whilst the ODD Gallery displays a variety of powerful photography and sculptural pieces produced by up and coming artists including Pierre Taurtaut who’s photography work is just beautiful. But the town itself is just as inspiring; the architecture, the atmosphere, the views. From the distinctive cobbled streets, to the abundance of floral archways and bronze statues, Saint Paul de Vence is truly worth visiting. Even before entering the Village itself, it’s worth taking a little detour through the hills where you’ll not only find the perfect view of Saint Paul, but also a number of abandoned and derelict chapels bringing a further element of mystery to the place. In regards to restaurants and cafes, I cannot recommend enough Restaurant Le Tilleul although I’ll admit, there’s often a waiting list depending on the time of year. I’ve always been impressed by the service and quality of food which explains why this restaurant in particular is so popular amongst both tourists and locals. But again, we’re honestly spoilt for choice when it comes to where and what we can eat. Saint Paul de Vence is perhaps one of the most impressive villages along the Cote d’Azur.</summary></entry></feed>